{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039874959","data":{"timestamp":" 947039874959"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 79df0348-fee8-47c4-9946-d65dbddf4eca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_73_73-102-105"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 73"," userResponse":" 73"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039882835","data":{"timestamp":" 947039882835"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 79df0348-fee8-47c4-9946-d65dbddf4eca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_70_48-97-70"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 70"," userResponse":" 70"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039898648","data":{"timestamp":" 947039898648"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 79df0348-fee8-47c4-9946-d65dbddf4eca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_80_80-73-100"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 80"," userResponse":" 80"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039905534","data":{"timestamp":" 947039905534"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 79df0348-fee8-47c4-9946-d65dbddf4eca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_65_65-97-55"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 65"," userResponse":" 65"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039941928","data":{"timestamp":" 947039941928"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 79df0348-fee8-47c4-9946-d65dbddf4eca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_109-46-95"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039952539","data":{"timestamp":" 947039952539"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 79df0348-fee8-47c4-9946-d65dbddf4eca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_54_56-82-54"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 54"," userResponse":" 54"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039966333","data":{"timestamp":" 947039966333"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 79df0348-fee8-47c4-9946-d65dbddf4eca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_98_98-83-54"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 98"," userResponse":" 98"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039978883","data":{"timestamp":" 947039978883"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 79df0348-fee8-47c4-9946-d65dbddf4eca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_103_88-108-103"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 103"," userResponse":" 103"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039990773","data":{"timestamp":" 947039990773"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 79df0348-fee8-47c4-9946-d65dbddf4eca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_49-68-95"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947039999279","data":{"timestamp":" 947039999279"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 79df0348-fee8-47c4-9946-d65dbddf4eca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_89-107-95"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040006916","data":{"timestamp":" 947040006915"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 79df0348-fee8-47c4-9946-d65dbddf4eca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_95_89-107-95"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040019835","data":{"timestamp":" 947040019835"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_73_73-106-70"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 73"," userResponse":" 73"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040028554","data":{"timestamp":" 947040028554"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_56_56-43-55"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 56"," userResponse":" 56"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040039204","data":{"timestamp":" 947040039204"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_103_88-108-103"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 103"," userResponse":" 103"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040047720","data":{"timestamp":" 947040047720"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_99_46-99-94"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 99"," userResponse":" 99"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040057962","data":{"timestamp":" 947040057962"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_71_90-77-71"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 71"," userResponse":" 71"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040065310","data":{"timestamp":" 947040065310"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_73_73-102-105"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 73"," userResponse":" 73"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040072726","data":{"timestamp":" 947040072726"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_66_66-60-86"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 66"," userResponse":" 66"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040082360","data":{"timestamp":" 947040082359"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_82_82-50-55"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 82"," userResponse":" 82"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040094263","data":{"timestamp":" 947040094262"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_70_48-97-70"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 70"," userResponse":" 97"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040101904","data":{"timestamp":" 947040101904"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_70_48-97-70"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 70"," userResponse":" 70"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040111858","data":{"timestamp":" 947040111858"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_63_56-82-63"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 63"," userResponse":" 63"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040119547","data":{"timestamp":" 947040119546"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 4aaedd90-4a63-41b4-bda7-43fe774e00ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_63_56-82-63"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040132241","data":{"timestamp":" 947040132241"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 0bce586d-68af-4f39-b622-6fd122f6662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_95_109-46-95"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 95"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040141965","data":{"timestamp":" 947040141965"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 0bce586d-68af-4f39-b622-6fd122f6662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_98_98-83-54"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 98"," userResponse":" 98"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040153627","data":{"timestamp":" 947040153627"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 0bce586d-68af-4f39-b622-6fd122f6662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_59_89-59-62"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 59"," userResponse":" 62"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040160730","data":{"timestamp":" 947040160730"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" 0bce586d-68af-4f39-b622-6fd122f6662b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_59_89-59-62"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040181134","data":{"timestamp":" 947040181133"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_92_90-92-95"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 92"," userResponse":" 90"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040192151","data":{"timestamp":" 947040192151"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_92_90-92-95"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 92"," userResponse":" 95"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040200163","data":{"timestamp":" 947040200163"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_92_90-92-95"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 92"," userResponse":" 92"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040207874","data":{"timestamp":" 947040207874"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_90_90-43-87"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 90"," userResponse":" 90"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040215349","data":{"timestamp":" 947040215349"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_80_80-73-100"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 80"," userResponse":" 73"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040222971","data":{"timestamp":" 947040222971"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_80_80-73-100"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 80"," userResponse":" 80"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040228686","data":{"timestamp":" 947040228686"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_66_66-60-86"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 66"," userResponse":" 66"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040235517","data":{"timestamp":" 947040235517"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_44_49-44-79"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 44"," userResponse":" 49"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040242421","data":{"timestamp":" 947040242421"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_44_49-44-79"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 44"," userResponse":" 44"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040252714","data":{"timestamp":" 947040252714"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_98_75-98-51"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 98"," userResponse":" 98"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040267716","data":{"timestamp":" 947040267716"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_73_73-102-105"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 73"," userResponse":" 73"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040297930","data":{"timestamp":" 947040297930"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_55_104-69-55"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 55"," userResponse":" 55"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040316921","data":{"timestamp":" 947040316921"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_56_56-92-101"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 56"," userResponse":" 56"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040326413","data":{"timestamp":" 947040326412"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_98_98-83-54"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 98"," userResponse":" 98"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040334180","data":{"timestamp":" 947040334179"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_98_98-83-54"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040345083","data":{"timestamp":" 947040345083"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_98_98-83-54"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040351384","data":{"timestamp":" 947040351384"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" d09ba1b9-199b-4c74-96b4-be2b5460538c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_40..99.MN-DD-UP-OFF2-BL2.decr.55"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_98_98-83-54"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040361185","data":{"timestamp":" 947040361185"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040361408","data":{"timestamp":" 947040361408"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040362370","data":{"timestamp":" 947040362370"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040363648","data":{"timestamp":" 947040363647"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040366573","data":{"timestamp":" 947040366572"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040367415","data":{"timestamp":" 947040367415"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040367729","data":{"timestamp":" 947040367729"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040368962","data":{"timestamp":" 947040368962"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040372536","data":{"timestamp":" 947040372536"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040373520","data":{"timestamp":" 947040373520"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040373773","data":{"timestamp":" 947040373773"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040374715","data":{"timestamp":" 947040374715"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040377561","data":{"timestamp":" 947040377560"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040378595","data":{"timestamp":" 947040378595"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040379068","data":{"timestamp":" 947040379068"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040383570","data":{"timestamp":" 947040383570"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040383630","data":{"timestamp":" 947040383630"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040392683","data":{"timestamp":" 947040392682"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:91..111.off2.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040444677","data":{"timestamp":" 947040444677"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:91..111.off2.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040494017","data":{"timestamp":" 947040494016"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:91..111.off2.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040535185","data":{"timestamp":" 947040535185"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:91..111.off2.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040575636","data":{"timestamp":" 947040575635"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:91..111.off2.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040619843","data":{"timestamp":" 947040619842"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:91..111.off2.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040666435","data":{"timestamp":" 947040666434"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:91..111.off2.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040709725","data":{"timestamp":" 947040709725"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:91..111.off2.28","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947040781451","data":{"timestamp":" 947040781451"," userId":" 6116002363"," sessionId":" 6116002363_20000105_053741"," gameId":" a7b7e3d4-0076-4281-9d1d-195a06e00dac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}